ID: 031117963

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/elichay-kaplan-15a915152

Frontend / Full Stack Web Developer with experience in writing single-page-applications using the latest WEB technologies, including React .js, Redux and Node.js.

Graduate of the Coding Academy - an intensive coding bootcamp (640 hours) that qualifies Full Stack developers.

Former Credit Operations Manager at HSBC Bank PLC.

My last project (Airbnb-like marketplace using React, Node, MongoDB):

https://akebnb-rental-service.onrender.com

Education:

2022-2023 Frontend / Full Stack Web Developer - Coding Academy (640 hours) 2003-2006 B.A in Economics, Bar-Ilan University

Experience:

2009-2022: Financial Analyst and Credit Operations Manager, HSBC Bank PLC

Credit and Accounts Operations Manager (2018-2022)

- o Responsibility over credit and accounts operations and accounts reconciliation.
- o Reports analysis Dealing and analyzing large amount of data and processes optimization.
- o Approving and signing financial activities in millions of dollars.
- o Escorting projects, define needs, applications implementations and guiding.
- Managing teams both onshore and offshore defining tasks, professional assistance.
- o Dealing complex situations improving working methods in dynamic environment.

Previous role within the department - Credit and Accounts Operations Officer

Financial Analyst and Reporting officer, Finance (2011-2017)

- o Profit and Loss reports analysis, creating complex reports and projections.
- o Reporting creating reports to head office in London, local management, and regulator.
- Maintain budget files, collect data alongside chief accountant.
- Accounts Control, reconciliation, daily liquidity and reports.
- Improving processes and systems, escorting offshoring activities.

Previous role within the organization - Operations Officer, Securities team.

2006-2008: Economist, Foreign currency department, Israel Discount Bank headquarters

o Member of SWIFT and RTGS team and responsible over the Bank's reconciliation system.

<u>Languages</u>: Hebrew – Mother tongue | English – Fluent.

Computer Applications: MS office, High Excel proficiency level (including Macro scripts).

Military Service: Serving in operational unit + one year standing army.

**Diplomas and recommendations will be provided upon demand.